Murder, She Baked: Just Desserts is a mystery, tv
movie film directed by Kristoffer Tabori.
Hannah Swensen is thrilled when she is chosen as a guest for the first Eden Lake Dessert Bake-Off, but when fellow
judge, Coach Bishop is found murdered, Hannah once again takes it upon herself to find the killer.
Hannah Swensen, played by Alison Sweeney.
Detective Mike Kingston, played by Cameron Mathison.
Delores Swensen, played by Barbara Niven.
Norman Rhodes, played by Gabriel Hogan.
Andrea Todd, played by Lisa Durupt.
Bill Todd, played by Toby Levins.
Murder, She Baked is an American/Canadian television film series based
on the cozy mystery novels written by Joanne Fluke.
The television films are centered around small-town baker Hannah Swensen, portrayed by
Alison Sweeney, and Detective Mike Kingston, played by Cameron Mathison.
Five films for the Hallmark Movies & Mysteries channel were created based on
Fluke's book series, with the fifth movie airing on March 26, 2017.
The films took a four-year hiatus before returning
as the Hannah Swensen Mysteries.
The films are set in the fictional town of Eden Lake in Minnesota,
reverting to Lake Eden like in the novels in the sixth film.
The tone is mind_bending.